我们深知 也很感激各位的投入
And not only do we hear and appreciate your input,
而且完全地承诺...
But we are fully committed...
给出百分之一百一十的努力 与毒品斗争...
To giving 110% in our efforts to fight this war against drugs...
将街道还给民众
And take back your streets.
但只靠我们是不够的
But we can't do it alone.
所以当你们看见违法行为 请拿起电话...
So when you see illegal activity, we need you to pick up the phone...
- 报警 好让我们得知 - 都是屁话
- And call it in so that we can get. - Man, that's bullshit!
请别急着提出质疑...
Please hold all your questions...
我685反毒电话都快打爆了 有什么用
I near wore out my phone dialing 685-Drug, and for what?
那些小鬼第二天照样出现
Those boys is back on the corner the next damn day!
这还是表明光靠警察是不够的
The fact remains that the police department can't do it alone.
我们需要市民的合作
We need your cooperation.
我堂兄Willy倒是合作了 他到市里作证
My cousin willy gant cooperated. He went downtown and testified.
- 结果死翘翘了 - 真可耻
- He deader than 2pac today. - Damn shame.
听着 我知道这问题看来难以克服...
Look, i know the problem seems insurmountable...
但我们已经初有成效了
But we are making progress.
看看这份图表
Take a look at this chart.
这条线表示...
This line here represents...
- 我在发言 女士 - 让她说
- I have the microphone, ma'am. - Let the woman speak.
我的孩子现在都不敢在外边玩了
My kids, they can't play outside no more.
有些晚上 我们听到枪声...
Some nights, when we hear these pops...
- 还得跑床底下睡觉 - 就是
- We got to sleep under our beds. - Right on.
我下班回家...
I come home from work...
连我家门前台阶都上不了...
I can't even get up my front steps...
因为台阶被毒贩占据了
'Cause they're occupied by the drug dealers.
就是 你告诉他
That's right, you tell him!
你那图上有这些吗
Is that in that picture you got up there?
我是Colvin警长
I'm major colvin.
我为今晚给了你们错误的印象抱歉
I apologize for giving you the wrong impression tonight.
我们并无不敬
We mean no disrespect.
我知道你们的社区发生着什么
I know what's going on in your neighborhoods.
我每天都能看见
I see it every day.
女士 您不能安全 带着尊严进自己的家门...
Ma'am, it pains me that you cannot enter your own front door in safety...
这让我心痛
And with dignity.
事实上...
The truth is...
我不能承诺情况会有好转
I can't promise you it's gonna get any better.
我们没法把街角那些小子们都抓起来
We can't lock up the thousands out there on the corners.
就算可以也没地方安置他们
There'd be no place to put them even if we could.
我们拿出图表 数据给你们看 好像这算什么东西
We show you charts and statistics like they mean something.
但你们今晚要回家...
But you're going back to your homes tonight...
我们要回到巡逻车上...
We're gonna be in our patrol cars...
那些小鬼还会在街角晃荡...
And them boys still gonna be out there on them corners...
热火朝天地贩毒
Deep in the game.
我们的世界就这么回事 各位
This here is the world we got, people.
我们这些心知肚明的人也该...
And it's about time all of us had the good sense...
至少面对现实了
To at least admit that much.
那答案是什么呢
So, what's the answer?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
但无论是什么 也不能是谎言
But whatever it is, it can't be a lie.
我还是第一次听到警察说出这些
First time i ever heard a cop say something like that.
交给你了 警司
It's all yours, sergeant.
正如我之前指出的...
As i was pointing out...
是谁给了他一罐汽油 让他灭火来着
Who gave him a can of gasoline and told him to put out the fire?
- 我们已有进展... - Tommy Carcetti
- We are making progress... - Tommy carcetti.
- Marla Daniels 我正在为... - 正在与Eunetta Perkins竞争
- Marla daniels. I'm running for... - Gonna take a run at eunetta perkins.
我知道你是谁
I know who you are.
我已经几次见你跟Watkins代表一起了
I've seen you with delegate watkins a couple of times already.
好吧 议员 这不是你的选区
Well, councilman, this is not your home district.
什么风把你吹到西区来的
What brings you to the west side?
我管理公共安全委员会... 所以
I got the public safety subcommittee...so
我就来了
Here i am.
无论如何 祝你拿下Eunetta
Anyway, good luck with eunetta.
还有 Daniels小姐 欢迎响应为民服务的崇高召唤
And welcome, miss daniels, to the noble calling of public service.
你们居住的远西区...
Further west in your neighborhoods...
针对商贩的犯罪率已大为下降
The numbers of crimes against merchants are way, way down.
我们相信我们正显著地...
We believe we're making significant...
- 这他妈算什么意思 - 我厌烦了那些屁话
- What the hell was that? - Tired of the bullshit.
厌烦到让你失去理智?
Tired make you lose your mind?
火线重案组 第三季 第四集 毒品合法地
The Wire S03E04 Amsterdam
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* He's got the fire and the fury *
* At his command *
* Well you don't have to worry *
* If you hold on to Jesus hand *
* We'll all be safe from Satan *
* When the thunder rolls *
* Just gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
"你们干嘛他妈的要破坏这个程序"  ---Fruit
你想让Bubs给你打探什么 我的意思是 说明确点
So, what you need from bubs? I mean, exactly?
地盘分配
The lay of the land.
高楼垮了 那个街角归谁
Who has what corners, now that the towers are down.
尤其想知道Barksdale的人什么情况
We wanna know what happened to the barksdale people, especially.
钱给得多吗
And this pay how much?
就当是一份实打实的工作吧 一小时五块
Let's treat it like a real job. Say $5 an hour.
一天顶多三十块
$30 on a day, max.
这可低于最低工资啊
That's less than minimum wage.
但那可是纯收入啊 Bubs 是免税的
But there's no withholding, bubs. It's tax-Free.
好吧 能出来不错 你知道?
All right. It feels good to be out here, you know?
我是说 有挣钱的活儿
I mean, gainfully employed.
- 还以为你朋友也要来呢 - Johnny?
- Thought your boy was coming, too. - Johnny?
他不愿跟你俩待一块儿
He don't think much of this here with y'all.
再说 他碰巧是...
Besides, he happens to be...
最懒的白人之一 油瓶倒了都不会扶的
One of the laziest white boys to ever shit between two shoes.
我呢 从小就出来工作了
Me, i've been working since i was a kid.
是吗 都干过什么工作啊
Yeah? What's your resume read like, bubs?
纯粹好奇
Just curious.
我可没做过有工资单的工作 Kima
Well, i ain't claiming no payroll jobs, kima.
我好久没打孔上下班了
It's been a while since i punched a clock.
那是什么时候的事儿了
When was that?
很久以前
Long time ago.
当时还没有前科
Before i had a sheet.
靠 我... 我当时还没吸毒
Shit, i was... i was still clean.
我找了个仓库的活儿...
I got one of those stock boy jobs...
一个"城里最便宜的家伙"的店
One of those "cheapest guys in town" stores.
卸电器...
Unloading appliances...
把空调什么的搬到客户车上
Taking air conditioners and shit out to the customers' cars.
这之类的
Like that.
"你想要多少?"
"How many you want?"
后来呢
What happened?
我一天把个定时收音机扔在垃圾桶里 想耍点小心机 被逮住了
I put a clock-Radio in the trashcan one day, trying to be cute, got caught.
我其实都不需要定时收音机
I didn't even need a clock-Radio.
看吧 这就是我 生来就要坏事的
See, that's me, though. Born fuck-Up.
好了 知道吗
All right, you know what?
一小时五块 一天三十块
$5 an hour, $30 on the day.
就这样吧
That'll work.
《Splash Waterfalls》 演唱：Ludacris
* Make love to me *
* Y'all do that bad stuff, she liked it rammed up *
* Ropes and hand cuffs *
* What?! Fuck me *
* I'm bout' to throw some gam, they both one and the same *
* Cupids the one to blame *
* Say it, make love to me *
* I'm 'bout to shed some light 'cause each and every night *
* You gotta do it right *
* What?! Fuck me... *
这个是你们的免死金牌
And this here is your "get out of jail free" card.
上面是我的全名和电话
On this card is my full name and phone number.
几周前一个警员在这附近中枪
A police officer was shot in this neighborhood a couple of weeks ago.
你们都知道我说的那件事 对吧
You all know the incident i'm speaking of, right?
我在找这名警员的配枪
I'm looking for the officer's gun.
一把格洛克9...
A glock 9...
在这事件中不小心放错了地儿
Which happened to misplace itself during this incident.
我不管...
Now, i don't care...
我不管它现在在谁手上
I don't care who has it now.
我只想把它找回来
I just need it to find its way home.
你们不会正好认识一个叫Peanut的家伙吧
Y'all don't happen to know a fellow by the name of peanut, right?
我想也是 无论如何 各位 你们知道 互惠互利
I didn't think so. Well, anyway, gentlemen, you know, one hand washes the other.
你们给我枪的线索 我能帮你们搞定几乎所有指控
You give me a good word on that gun and i can make almost any charge disappear.
- 有问题吗 - 啊?
- Any questions? - Huh?
让他们散了吧
Get them out.
靠 我总得试试吧
Shit, i had to try something.
一人一个 一人一个
One each. One each.
动起来 小鬼们 这儿全天供应黄盖
Keep it moving. Little boys. Yellow tops all day long. Right here.
好 好 来看他顺便拿点好东西 对吧
All right, all right. Come and see him and get that knockout shit, all right?
非常感激 很漂亮
Much obliged. Good looking.
- 嘿 他占着Fremont? - 对
- Yo, he down across fremont? - Yeah.
对 现在我们都在这边
Now we're on this side.
而Barksdale在这条路后边
Oh, and barksdale is down the way.
来要红盖 来啊 红盖
Got the red tops, y'all, red tops!
蜘蛛包
Spider bags here!
好家伙
My nigga.
嘿 蜘蛛包
Yo, spider bags!
来点红盖 红盖
Come get the red tops, red tops!
- 重案组 - 看看
- Major crimes unit. - Look at that.
- 慢慢地... - 他现在不在
- It's slowly... - he's not in right now.
- 好的 - 我们何以有此荣幸
- All right. - To what do we owe the honor?
来报个到
Just checking in.
干嘛 有什么进展
Why? You got something going on?
没什么太刺激的 只是在一点点地...
Nothing too sexy. Just pushing a case uphill...
查Kintel Williamson的案子...
Inch by inch on kintel williamson...
我们的既定目标
Our stated target.
- 我们也在干活 Lester - 是啊 干你们自己的活
- We're working, too, lester. - Yeah, on your own thing.
在听我说话吗 McNulty?
You even listening to me, mcnulty?
我有个大案子要跟进
I got a real case to bring in.
追查一个叫Stringer Bell的人 你也许听说过 我也不确定
Fellow name of stringer bell. You might have heard of him. I don't know.
你牙尖嘴利啊 小子
You got a mouth on you, boy.
他还逍遥法外 Lester
He's still out there, lester.
有自己的地盘 赚着钞票
He's got his corners, his money.
去他的吧 目前为止 就你们所知 他拥有市区所有的房产
Fuck it. By now, for all you know, he's got all that downtown real estate.
那混球可能拥有半个Baltimore...
Motherfucker probably owns half of baltimore...
- 而我们还一无所知 - 这不是重点
- Without us even knowing it. - That ain't the point.
你知道那些房产怎么样了吗 Lester?
Do you even know what happened to all that real estate, lester?
那些Bell名下市区的房产?
All that downtown property bell has title on?
靠 不知道吧
Fuck, no.
他现在大概鸟蛋都笑出来了 笑你 我 Daniels 我们所有人
He's probably laughing his balls off right now. At you, me, daniels, all of us.
你还以为你能替这里其他人说话了 McNulty?
You even pretending to speak for anyone other than yourself, mcnulty?
- 我在说工作 - 你想说警察工作?
- I'm speaking for the job. - You wanna talk about police work?
你还做梦想当警察时我就已经是警察了
I was doing the job when you was just dreaming on it.
Daniels也是
Daniels was out there, too.
现在他把你从水警弄回来 你却要摆他一道?
Now, you gonna fuck him when he pulled you off a goddamn boat?
他是老大 老大都不是好东西
He's a boss. Fuck the bosses.
也许Daniels耍了些手段...
Maybe daniels plays a few games to get by...
但他围着工作付出了很多
But he's cost himself plenty for the sake of the job!
他需要得到你们的忠诚
He's earned some loyalty.
去他的忠诚 去你的 Lester 我从没想过我会听到...
Fuck loyalty and fuck you, lester. I never thought i'd hear...
指挥链这种屁话从你嘴里吐出来
That chain-Of-Command horseshit come out of your mouth.
混球 我在很多无聊的岗位上 浪费了大把的时间
Motherfucker, i've spent a lot of time in a lot of weak units.
比你还多
More than you.
这里也许不够完美 但有机会做个警察
Now, this here may not be perfect, but it's a chance to be police.
那就做个警察
Well, then be one.
你不配我揍你 小鬼
You're not even worth the skin off my knuckles, junior.
Jimmy 不要
Jimmy, don't.
你见着什么就放火 McNulty...
You put fire to everything you touch, mcnulty...
然后走开看着它烧
Then you walk away while it burns.
我跟你没什么可说的了
I got nothing more to say to you.
没有
Nothing.
而你...
And you...
我很诧异 孩子
I'm surprised at you, girl.
Daniels把你培养成才
Daniels raised you from a pup.
去找Bubs
Gotta get with bubs.
去查查那些该死的房产
Check on those fucking properties.
Colvin警长 你觉得怎样
Well, major colvin, what do you think?
听起来不错
Well, it all sounds good.
但我得跟妻子谈谈才能答复你
But before i give you a final answer, i need to speak with my wife.
我说的不是职位
I'm not talking about the position.
是说你的酪饼
Your cheesecake.
酪饼不错
The cheesecake's fine.
他们从York路那边的Michael's弄来的
They bring it in from michael's, out on york road.
面包片上有些肉桂
It's got a little cinnamon in the crust.
世间美味
None better.
当然 我觉得我们的提议也不错
Of course, i'd like to think our offer's pretty damn good, too.
二位 失陪 我要去趟小朋友间
Excuse me while i go to the little boys' room, gentlemen.
我要嘘嘘
I need to tinkle.
嘘嘘?
Tinkle?
我就想不通干嘛一个成年人要那样说话
I never understood why a grown- Ass man gotta talk like that.
不管他知不知道 他只是要小个便
He need to take a piss, whether he know it or not.
你会习惯这种术语的 Bunny
You'll get used to these academic types, bunny.
尤其在你拿到第一笔薪水后
Especially when you get that first paycheck.
我是说 八万对于一个 二号安保工作来说没什么嗤之以鼻的
I mean, 80 k is nothing to sneeze at for a number-Two security job.
远高于你的退休金
Full bennies on top of your pension.
嗯 是挺多的
Yeah, it's generous.
还无聊 也是好事
And dull. In a good way.
我是说...
I mean...
你能遇上的最糟的也就是强奸 也许是约会强暴
The worst you'll ever see is a rape. A date rape, maybe.
你准备低调行事了 不是吗
You're ready to take it down a notch, aren't you?
- 该死 没错 - 嗯 我也是这么想的
- Hell, yes. - Yeah, that's how i felt.
我唯一的遗憾就是走的时候...
My only regret was that i didn't tell the deputy ops...
没把副局长臭骂一顿
To stick it in his ass on my way out the fucking door.
嘿 Johns Hopkins想雇你 Bunny
Hey, johns hopkins wants you, bunny.
而他们也愿付Johns Hopkins钱
And they wanna pay johns hopkins money.
但怎么
But what?
你还要问你老婆?
You gotta ask your wife?
伙计 我不会问她的 我只是...
Oh, man, i ain't gotta ask her nothing. I'm just..
我只是考验考验Jenkins先生的耐心
I'm just letting mr. Jenkins stew a little, is all.
他怎么还没来
Wonder what's keeping him.
不过是嘘嘘一下
All he had to do was tinkle.
我猜他觉得还得嘟滴一下
I guess he felt the need to make a dookie, too.
他们占据了从Argyle街角...
They got corners up on argyle...
一直到Fremont街的尽头
And along fremont up top.
大街街角是大家共享的
Avenue corners belong to everybody.
有些是Barksdale的人 有些貌似单干
Some who were with barksdale, and some independent-Like.
Mchenry街也有些Barksdale的人
Mchenry street got some of barksdale's people, too.
不过土匪Webster的人就在他们旁边
But gangster webster's crew is right beside them.
那较小的街角和筒子楼那边呢
What about the lower avenue corners and the poe homes?
他们归一个叫Marlo的年轻人
They belong to this young boy named marlo.
- 又叫Black - Marlo?
- Go by the name of black. - Marlo?
年轻人
Young boy.
近市区的好房产都是他的
Got all that good real estate near downtown.
可是赚的盆满钵满啊
Got himself the lunchtime trade.
如果Bell和Barksdale要掌控什么...
If bell and barksdale were gonna hold anything...
肯定要掌控筒子楼和街角
They'd hold on to the homes and avenue corners.
Marlo是Barksdale的人?
Marlo one of barksdale's people?
全名是什么
Marlo what?
说吧 你还有这家伙的什么消息
Come on, you got anything else on this guy?
你小费是不是还能再给点
You got another tip, maybe?
每小时工钱看来没法让你满足啊
So much for the hourly wage.
107M703 嗯
107m703. Yeah.
他开的卡车的车牌号
That's the tag on the truck he ride.
107M703
107m703.
你灌满了没
Did you prime it?
那边那个小橡皮球 火花塞旁那个
That little rubber ball right there, next to the spark plug.
你启动前要先把它推进去三次
You gotta push it in three times before you try to start it.
让汽油流进化油器
Gets the gas going to the carb.
想听实话吗 我从没用过这些东西
You want the truth? I ain't never used one of these.
也没必要做这种事情
Never had no call to.
嗯 我找你又不是为了你的园艺技能
Yeah, well, i didn't pick you up for your landscaping skills.
这些个西班牙人? 他们也有前科
All these spanish? They own paper, too.
我只雇你们这样的人
I only use people like y'all.
有时会坏事 有时结果也不坏
Sometimes it comes back on me, sometimes it works out fine.
- 你来住宅区多久了 - 10年
- For how long you been uptown? - 10 years.
这天儿热得比那些混球还让人受不了
Hotter than a motherfucker out here.
嗯 是挺热的 每天都是
Yeah, it's hot. Every day.
你得坐在卡车后面 上下颠簸...
You gonna be riding in the back of that hard truck, bouncing around...
每天都是
Every day.
你的背每天都会跟你抱怨
And your back's gonna be yelling at you every day.
我以前开一辆SL
I used to drive an sl.
很炫的金色敞篷车 轮辋很好
Pretty gold convertible. Nice rims.
我现在都不去想那车了
I don't even think on that car no more.
你已经向前看了 对吧?
You put it behind you, huh?
有些时候可以
Some can.
我是说 你想走回正道...
I'm just saying, you wanna stay on the straight...
不会因此得到大奖
Ain't gonna be no big reward to it.
你能得到的就是这样 就这些
This is it, right here.
灌注三次 它就能开工了
Prime that bitch three times. She'll start right up.
- Pearlman小姐? - Cedric
- Miss pearlman? - Cedric.
Kintel Williamson查得怎样了
How goes kintel williamson?
- 有什么消息能提供给我的 - 还没有
- Anything there for me yet? - No, not yet.
会有的
We'll get there.
你到访就为告诉我这些?
Is that all you came by to tell me?
只是要保持沟通而已
Just keeping the lines of dialogue open.
你这儿什么情况
So, what's on your plate?
这儿到处是惊喜
Oh, there's plenty of surprises around here.
假释听证会
Parole hearing.
这么快?
This soon?
显然他在Jessup揭发了一个腐败警卫
He fingered a dirty guard up at jessup, apparently.
得了一朵小红花呢
Got a big gold star next to his name.
- 真是狗屁 - 嗯 不过不用担心
- That's some bullshit. - Yeah, well, not to worry.
他们寄给我听证会通知是有原因的
They send me the hearing notifications for a reason.
"Barksdale经营一个 长期的暴力犯罪团伙..."
"Mr. Barksdale ran a continuous violent criminal enterprise...
"也是一个重要毒贩"
And was a major drug trafficker.
"在1999年至2002年间..."
During the years 1999 to 2002...
"严重涉嫌指使并导致了..."
He was strongly suspected to have ordered or caused...
"多人死亡"
The deaths of over a dozen individuals."
假释委员会不会让他得偿所愿的
Parole commission's not gonna walk him on his first trip to the plate.
至少看完这封信后不会
Not after a letter like that.
- 干得好 - 我也有两把刷子的
- Good work. - I have my moments.
顺便一说 衣服不错
Nice suit, by the way.
谢谢
Thanks.
看来你是放左边的
I see you dress left.
天天见咯
Every day.
您所拨打的电话已停机
The number you have called is no longer in service.
如果您认为您收到的这段录音有误...
If you feel you've reached this recording in error...
请查清号码再拨...
Please check the number and dial...
没有收获?
Nothing?
这是个Reisterstown的地址 两年前他也是用这个...
That's an address up off of reisterstown, same one he was showing two years ago...
当我查他开的车时
When i ran the car he was using.
- Stringer有固定居所 - 但不住那
- Stringer's a settled guy. - Not there, he ain't.
我之前查 有个女人住那 只有名
Woman living there, last time i checked. Just a front name.
也许是他女友
His girl, maybe.
除非他喜欢年过五十奇丑无比的女人
Not unless he likes them over 50 and asshole-Ugly.
不过我肯定她人挺好
I'm sure she's real nice, though.
有书卷气 会在走廊跟你问好
Good school spirit. Always says hi to you in the halls.
你认为他跟她在大学认识的?
You think he met her in college?
干嘛 我说什么了
What? What did i say?
查到什么了
What you got?
由车牌查到个Dukeland的地址
Tag comes back to an address over on dukeland.
- 女性 53岁 - 看见了? 他们都这么干
- Female, 53 years. - See? That's how they do.
对 但我查到了Marlo 花名Black
Yeah, but i got a hit on a marlo, street name of black.
Marlo Stanfield
Marlo stanfield.
22岁
22 years.
有BPI电话号记录
Bpi number
记录良好
And a pretty good sheet.
怎么 你觉得他是个初哥?
What, you thought he'd be cherry?
我知道他已经破处了 但不是这个
Oh, i knew he'd have his cherry busted, but not like this.
你看
Check it out.
我觉得要去凶杀科走一趟 你要去吗
Think i'm gonna take a ride downtown to homicide. Wanna come?
不 我要去别的地儿
Nope, got someplace to be.
跟Lester的龃龉...
This thing with lester...
我觉得不好受
I feel like shit about it.
你会习惯的
Well, you'll get used to it.
我们到了那 下车
We roll up and we get out of the car.
围观群众就像红色海洋 被害人躺在地上 血流满地...
Crowd parts like the red sea, victim's on the ground, bleeding all over the place...
叫嚷着 "我要杀了那人渣"
Screaming, "i'm gonna kill that fucking bitch."
但是好像他一点问题都没有...
But it's like nothing's really wrong with him...
该死
Oh, shit.
你想躲着我 不是吗
You tried to sneak by me, didn't you?
我只是安静而充满敬意的走进来
I was just coming in quiet and respectful.
对个大胖子来说 你确有舞者的优雅
Well, for a big man, you do have a dancer's grace.
但我 先生 我可有鹰的眼睛
But i, sir, i have the eyes of an eagle.
不过你妄图不被察觉地进入工作地点...
And the fact that you tried to slither into your work space undetected...
表明我们寻找丢失的手枪的前景 仍不乐观啊 不是吗
Does not bode well for the recovery prospect of our missing firearm, does it?
我会找回来的
I'll get it.
- 你好啊 Bunk先生? - 嘿 女朋友
- What up, mr. Bunk? - Hey, girlfriend.
- Vernon Holley今晚上班吗 - 对 他4:00到12:00当班
- Vernon holley working tonight? - Yeah, he's 4:00 to 12:00.
你可以去咖啡间找找
You should try the coffee room.
好的
All right.
伙计 我真想...
Man, i would murder that...
- 如果她不那么... - 独特?
- If she wasn't... - Particular?
嘿 Crossfield 在闪那一线是找你的
Hey, crossfield, that line that's blinking's for you.
- 把枪找回来 - 好啦
- Find that gun. - Yeah, okay.
去你妈的
Mother fuck you, too.
Marlo Stanfield 又名Black
Marlo stanfield, a.K.A. Black.
他可是恶魔之子 Kima
Boy's the spawn of the devil, kima.
了解
I see.
你们差点就能将他定罪谋杀
And y'all damn near had him on this murder.
怎么回事
What happened?
他很聪明
We had a wit.
有个人称Pooh Bear的扎小辫的胖子
Boy they called pooh bear, chubby fellow with braids.
我们把他藏在东Baltimore...
We stashed pooh over in east baltimore...
还给他带上电子手铐...
Even had him wear one of those electronic bracelets...
好能迅速找到他
So we could find him quick.
- 你们把他丢了? - 也不全是
- You lost him? - Not exactly.
Pooh跑回西区偷点水种的大麻
Pooh went back to the west side to cop some hydro.
那毒品在哪都能买 对吧
He could've bought the same weed where he was, right?
我们发现他时 两颗子弹在他胸腔 一颗直接射在嘴里
We found him with two in his chest and one in his mouth.
我们通过手拷找到他葬身之处
The bracelet led us right to the spot where he fell.
那东西还挺管用
Those things work.
嗯 Marlo真有种
Yeah. Marlo's serious.
那混球够狠
That motherfucker's real.
我不知道 我觉得火山比电脑强
I don't know, i think a volcano's way better than a computer.
你每天都能看到电脑 看见火山能有多频繁
You see computers every day. How often do you see a volcano?
是啊 但那家伙做了台电脑
Yeah, but that guy built the computer.
嘿 你做了个火山
Hey, you built the volcano.
多大的事
Big whoop.
能送给我吗
Can i keep it?
你要就拿去
Yeah, if you want to.
- 晚安 Mikey - 晚安
- Good night, mikey. - Good night.
- 睡个好觉 - 好的
- Sleep tight. - Okay.
你能来真好
It's good that you came.
- 他很自豪 - 应该的
- He was very proud. - Glad to.
Jimmy 抚养费有点问题
Jimmy, there's a problem with the alimony.
什么问题
What's the problem?
你有四个月没给了
You're behind by like four months.
我能怎么说 我每月开销两千
What can i tell you? I'm paying $2,000 a month in support.
然后就没剩多少了
After that, there's nothing left.
没错 但你签了分居协议 每个月再付一千抚养费
Right. But you signed a separation agreement that gives me another $1,000 in alimony.
Elena 我签那个是因为以为我们能复合
Elena, i only signed that fucking thing 'cause i thought we'd be together.
看看我能挣多少 每月那么多我肯定付不起
Look at how much i make. I'm not even close to being able to pay that much every month.
我的律师说我们该给你传票
My lawyer says that we have to serve you.
怎么 那个西装男友就不能多少出点?
What, that suit of a boyfriend won't cough up any cash?
缘木求鱼啊 亲爱的
Blood from a stone, darling.
从今天开始...
Beginning today...
能在西Baltimore贩毒...
You can sell drugs in west baltimore...
但只能在我们许可的地方
But only where we say you can.
逼得紧点
Push them hard.
行动吧 伙计们 但别被逮到
Get to it, people, and don't get captured.
嘿 待在那
Hey! Stay right there.
让他面墙站着
Get him up against the wall.
嘿 给我听清楚了
Hey, listen to what i'm telling you.
* I know they told you i was stubborn, i bend them walls *
* That's the only reason you back in in the circle of drugs *
* I give you what you need, girl, i stroke your... *
你们知道 小子们...
You know, kids...
我们要说的很简单
This is a simple fucking thing we're saying here.
如果你们待在这街角 就得东躲西藏
If you stay on this corner, you're going in a wagon.
如果你们搬到自由区...
If you move yourself down to the free zone...
Vincent街那片无人区...
Down to the vacants along vincent street...
你们想干嘛都成
Then you can do whatever the fuck you want!
能比现在自由多少啊?
How much fairer can we be?
嘿 我看见了 你这小混蛋 你叫什么名字
Hey, i saw that, you little fuck. What's your name?
你有名字吗
You got a name?
花生酱 果冻
Peanut butter and jelly.
- 地址? - 哈?
- Address? - Huh?
你住哪?
What's your address?
我待在Dolphin街
I stay over on dolphin street.
- 你的地址 呆子 - 哈?
- Your address, numb nuts. - Huh?
你他妈家门口有什么数字
Are there any numbers on the front of your fucking house?
听好了
Listen up.
在这街角犯事儿会被指控
This corner is indicted.
我们明天再来 来的时候见一个抓一个...
We're coming back tomorrow, and when we do, everybody wears bracelets...
除非你们搬到Vincent街...
Unless you move your shit down to vincent street...
那些无人的房子里
Down where the houses are all vacant.
你们这么做 我们就不管
You do that, we don't give a shit!
Vincent街就如瑞士和阿姆斯特丹
Vincent street is like switzerland or amsterdam.
那是什么东西
What the fuck is that?
是毒品合法的国家
It's one of those countries where drugs are legal.
Vincent街就是你们在Baltimore的 阿姆斯特丹
Vincent street is your amsterdam in baltimore.
你们到那去 我们就不干涉 待在这 就得去坐牢
You go down there, we don't give a fuck. You stay here, you go to jail.
我才不去什么阿姆斯特丹
I ain't going to no hamsterdam.
他杀了个证人?
He killed a witness, huh?
照Vernon Holley的说法是这样
The way that vernon holley told it, yeah.
这么说Marlo是个杀手
So marlo's a hitter.
也许他为Stringer做事
Maybe he works for stringer.
有道理
Makes sense.
如果找我 我在西区
If you need me, i'm gonna be west side.
你呢
What about you?
我得探探Stringer的风声
I gotta get the scent of my boy, stringer.
我们远离他太久了
We've been off him too long.
- 你第一步要做什么 - 做Prez说的事
- What's your first move? - Something prez said.
"PP"?
"P and p"?
BB 就像是那个酒名
B and b. Like the liquor.
你是说那个利口酒呢吧 Plauzinski...
You mean, liqueur, plauzinski...
- Pryzbylewski - Benedictine和Brandy
- Pryzbylewski. - Benedictine and brandy.
21俱乐部的一个酒保发明的
That was invented by a bartender over at club 21.
那些好东西都出自纽约
All that good shit comes out of new york.
我要所有有关那公司的转让契约 Harry
I need every deed transfer involving that company, harry.
今天就要
Today.
我问那些小子Barksdale的货哪有
Yo, i'm asking them corner boys if they know where the barksdale package be at.
他们看着我好像我在放屁
And they looking at me like i ain't even talking.
在这地头 Marlo名声最响
On this strip, marlo's the name ringing out.
那就是他 看见没
There he is. You see him?
- 他没停留多久 - 对 Marlo神龙见首不见尾
- He didn't stay too long. - Yeah, marlo's ghosting.
透露录取学生的个人信息可不符合规定啊
We're kind of sensitive about giving out personal data on matriculating students.
我可以拿个法庭命令过来
Well, i could come back with a court order.
- 那我到时就不得不给你看了 - 你看
- Then i'd have to give it to you. - Look.
我朋友不太喜欢女人
My man has serious issues with women.
家庭暴力什么的 极其丑恶
Domestic violence, really ugly stuff.
文件我是不能给你看的
I can't show you any paper.
但我可以给你瞅瞅屏幕
But let me get my screen up.
我们说什么来着 我们他妈的说什么来着
What did we tell you? What'd we fucking tell you, man?
我们说了让你们到自由区去 不是吗
We told you to get yourselves down to the free zone, didn't we?
我们也不想一直缠着你们
We're trying to give you guys a break.
我们给你们提供...
We're offering you...
- 什么来着 - 特赦
- What's that? - Amnesty.
你带着你的人到Vincent街
You take your crew down to vincent street.
干你们的勾当 没人鸟你
You do your dirt, nobody's gonna bother you.
你们怎么说
What do you say?
你们他妈的脑残了? 你们怎么说
You guys fucking brain-Dead? What do you say?
嘿 长官 你们干嘛要跑来这耍我们
Yo, chief, how you gonna come up here and try to game us?
你说什么
Say what?
我说你们当我们是弱智吗...
I'm saying you acting like we retarded or something...
- 我们该踹你们一脚? - 至少那比较好理解
- Better we put a foot in your ass? - At least we'd understand it.
这不是玩阴的 傻鸟
This ain't a trick, shitbird!
你看 我们干活 你们阻止 我们就这样
Look, we grind, and y'all try to stop it. That's how we do.
你们干嘛他妈的要破坏这个程序
Why you gotta go and fuck with the program?
没想顶撞你啊
All due respect.
除了杂草啥都没有
Nothing but tumbleweeds.
给我找些大巴
Get me some buses.
明天就扫荡街角
Tomorrow we clean the corners.
把他们都弄到一块告诉他们这消息
Put them all in one place and give them the news.
这是命令
And i'm not asking anymore.
从这到Fremont...
From here to fremont...
有Barksdale的人 东区的小子 和一些单干的
You got barksdale's people, east siders and freelancers, too.
- 共用街角? - 对
- On the same corners? - Yup.
这说不通啊
That shit don't make sense.
嘿 今天到此为止行吗 Kima?
Yo, can we call it a day, kima?
我靠
Bullshit, man.
你也来?
You, too?
这些电话怎么着了
What the fuck is up with these phones?
我成天见小鬼们乱扔
I've been seeing kids throwing them away all day.
他们有那么多钱拿来浪费?
They got cash like that to waste?
这些东西到处都是 伙计 有时好运捡一个
Them shits be laying all over, man. Sometimes you get lucky.
还有几分钟可用 卖了可以赚点小钱
Find some minutes on them, sell them for walking-Around money.
- 这些是即用即弃的 Kima - 即用即弃?
- They burners, kima. - Burners?
Marron 又一个凶手 还在Waverly 你能相信吗
Marron, another murder. In waverly, no less. You believe it?
如果这是非裔美国人犯下的 我会深表震惊的
I would be fucking shocked if it was an african-American perpetrated the crime.
这不好笑 Ash
It ain't even funny, ash.
就因为这样无论黑人白人都要离开这城市
This is why everyone's leaving this city, black and white.
我周日在西Baltimore参加了个社区集会
I was at a community meeting, sunday, in west baltimore.
人们都很激动 我不得不说不是他们的错
People were spitting mad, and i can't say i blame them.
他们可以搬到个更好的社区
Well, they could move to a better neighborhood.
如果他们愿意为此努力的话
That is...If they were willing to work for it.
拜托 我一辈子都听着 "我贫穷的移民父亲做得到..."
Come on, i've been hearing that "my poor immigrant father made it...
"为什么黑人就不行"这类屁话
"So why can't the blacks?"  Bullshit my whole life.
他们觉得西区就没好人...
Think there's not good people on the west side...
- 他们追求的跟你们... - 好了 罗斯福太太
- Who want the same things that you... - Okay, mrs. Roosevelt.
我想说的是 这与肤色无关
All's i'm saying is, it's not about color.
你下一步想怎么办 Tommy?
So what's your next move, tommy?
太阳报称一个叫Anderson的 州议员的位子虚位以待
The sun says an anderson state senate seat is up for grabs.
去他的 你很快可以接Ruppersberger的班
Fuck that, you could go after ruppersberger in the second.
他只有一届任期
He's only got one term.
我要竞选市长
I'm gonna run for mayor.
很好 Tommy市长
That's good. Mayor tommy.
她来对地方了?
Is she in the right joint?
她让我坐她旁边 我请她喝酒...
She lets me sit next to her, i buy her a drink...
我们就每人给你十块 如果你干了她就二十
We each give you $10. $20 if you fuck her.
- 拜托 Ash - 不要那么低级行不
- Oh, please, ash. - Show just a little more class.
再说 我今天也衣冠楚楚过了
Besides, i already had my day in the sun.
放屁 Tommy
Bullshit, tommy.
- 一个负伤的猎犬... - 赌归赌 你们说我不知所措
- Once a gash-Hound... - The bet is the bet. You said i lost a step.
我就要证明我没有
I'm gonna prove i never did.
- 你加入吗 Pete? - 我就算了
- You in, pete? - I'll pass.
能给我来两杯Glenlivets吗
Can i have two glenlivets?
你好
How you doing?
- 那狗娘养的还真办到了 - 他耍了你俩
- The son of a bitch did it. - He did you.
那是Theresa D'agostino Mario D的孩子
That's theresa d'agostino. Mario d's kid?
对 她长大了 来特区了...
Yeah, she grew up all right. She's down in dc now...
加入国家党 做竞选掮客
With the national party. A campaign fixer.
不是吧
No shit.
Tommy在法学院时就认识她了
Tommy's known her ever since law school.
听我说完 好吗 就一杯
Just hear me out, okay? One drink.
请啊 你付钱
Go ahead. You're paying for it.
- 事实上 是他们付的 - 你们打赌了
- Actually, they are. - You made a bet.
别告诉我还得接吻什么的 不可能
Don't tell me we have to kiss or something. Not gonna happen.
这可不是在个二点五星级的酒店 玩鞋搭扣 对吧
This isn't about ankle straps in a two-And-A-Half star hotel, is it?
因为校友聚餐一小时前就结束了 而我现在就该回到特区...
Because the alumni dinner ended an hour ago and i could be back in dc right now...
那是过去的我了 Terri
That's the old me, terri.
我现在有妻有子...
Everything i got now, my wife, my kids...
我不会冒失去他们的风险 不会
I would not risk losing them. No way.
看见你又玩老把戏 又想起了从前
Seeing you with your old gang made me think bad thoughts.
你朋友轻贱你 Tommy
Your friends cheapen you, tommy.
你只是不高兴自己进来时他们没认出你
You're just pissed off that they didn't recognize you when you walked in.
他们怎么认得出
And why would they?
我是说 你现在是华盛顿人了
I mean, you're a washingtonian now.
那边的是Pete Sinopoli不是吗
That's pete sinopoli over there, isn't it?
- 听说他回来做执业律师了 - 对
- I hear he's back to practicing law. - Yeah.
他只是不得其时 对吧
He just didn't have it, did he?
我得其时了 Terri
I have it, terri.
我要竞选市长
I'm gonna make a run for mayor.
而你该来替我主持竞选
And you're gonna run my campaign.
给我一个不这么做的理由
Give me one good reason why not to.
我能给你十个 不过这就有个好的
I could give you 10, but here's the good one.
你肤色不对 你在这选不上的
You're the wrong color. You're not electable here.
- 而我不喜欢高风险 - 你喜欢赢
And i never play the long shot. You like to win.
我不喜欢输 这是两码事
I don't like to lose. It's not the same thing.
如果你早知会赢那还有什么意思
Where's the fun in it if you know you're gonna win?
你在东洛杉矶帮的那个民主党员 他什么名字来着...
I mean, you handled that democrat in east la, what was his name...
- Garcia... - Valdez
- Garcia... - valdez.
Valdez 那有多难
Valdez. How hard was that?
我这边需要你这样的人
I need someone like you on my side.
我需要你
I need you.
获胜奖金有多少
How big a win bonus?
在Baltimore让一个白人选上市长 亲爱的
Get a white mayor elected in baltimore,honey,
你说多少就多少
You name your price.
你这是发酒疯呢
One drink was the deal.
回家去 睡一觉
Go home, sleep it off.
第二天醒来你就会发现你犯了个错误
You'll wake up and realize you're making a mistake.
我能做到的
I can do this.
问题是 你会追随我吗
Question is, are you gonna come with me?
BB
B and b.
喂?
Hello?
我们怎么不给那些混蛋几枪
Yo, how we not gonna throw a few hot ones at the motherfuckers?
一顿揍我们就像贱货似地跑了
One ass-Whupping and we back off like some bitches.
接着来到这个鸟不拉屎的地方
Then we on this off-Brand-Ass strip right here.
连给Poot和他的人塞牙缝的生意都不够 这太扯淡了 伙计
Ain't even enough trade for poot and his crew. This some bullshit, man!
听着 伙计 Stringer会处理的 看着吧
Look, man, stringer gonna fix it, man, you'll see.
你们谁是Slim Charles?
Which one of y'all is slim charles?
- 你是谁 - 我是Cutty
- Who asking? - That'd be cutty.
你们的人给我个号码 说等我准备好接些活了...
Your boy gave me a number, said to ring you up...
就联系你们 结果却没人接听
When i was ready to put in some work. But no answer.
你等了很久才打的 对吧
Took your time calling back, right?
那些号码几天就作废了 伙计
The numbers don't play after a few days, man.
- 我们会换号 - 就是 你什么都不懂吗
- We change them up. - Yeah, ain't you know nothing?
放尊重点 小子 你不知道你在跟谁说话
Respect, dawg, respect. Y'all don't know who y'all talking to, man.
- 你还没说你做的是什么事呢 伙计 - 我想干点活
- You still ain't say your business, man. - I'm trying to get put on.
- 你有什么想法 - 你能付得起的就行
- What you got in mind? - Whatever you got that pays.
嘿 Poot 过来 伙计
Yo, poot. Come here, man.
听着 伙计 打给Shamrock...
Hey, look, man, call shamrock, man...
告诉他士兵终于归队了
And tell him soldier's finally came into the camp.
- 你是个战士啊? - 冷静 哥们 别激动
- You a soldier, huh? - Chill, bodie, man, chill, man.
Broadus老弟?
Oh, bodie broadus?
嗯 是我
Yeah, that's right.
靠 你还穿尿布时我还见过你的小屁屁
Shit, i remember your little ass when you was still in diapers.
我跟你大哥干过一架 James
I used to spar with your older brother, james.
那小子活脱脱一杀手
That boy had a killer left.
嗯 他以前是挺牛的
Yeah, when he ain't drop it.
嘿 他还在混吗
Yo, he still out here?
James挂了
James been dead.
那些奶酪盒是个什么情况
Fuck's up with that cheese box?
怎么 你从没坐过校车吗
What, you ain't never ridden no school bus before?
我是说 他们要把那些街角的黑鬼弄哪去
I'm saying, what they doing with the niggas on that corner?
听着 伙计 我们得先给你弄个号
Look, dawg, first thing we gonna need to do is get you some chrome.
走吧 伙计
Look, come on, man.
我的电话怎么了
What's wrong with my fucking phone?
靠
Shit.
嘿 TJ 你还有能打几分钟的吗
Yo, tj, you got one with some minutes left?
这并不能说明 你不能拿Howard街的房产...
Which is not to say that you couldn't do some multi-Use...
做些别的
With the howard street properties, too.
- 商业 居住两用不错 - 在Howard街?
- Residential-Commercial could work. - On howard street?
联邦补助是要...
The whole point of the block grant is to...
让西区变成高端区域
Bring the west side back to make it high-End.
体育场工程只是个开始 懂吗
The hippodrome project was just the start, see?
但居住区呢?
But residential?
一旦体育场和剧院投入运作...
With the stadium and the theater back on line...
整个区域就会像10年前的内港东部
That whole area is like inner harbor east 10 years ago.
重点是凭你的房产 你就一路领先
And the thing is, you're on the ground floor with what you're holding.
对 就是 String
Yes, you are, string.
所以我们说的...
So we're still talking more return...
是比卖掉那些被征用房产赚的更多的钱
Than just flipping the properties for the condemnation money.
多很多
Way more.
不好意思
Excuse me.
喂
Yo.
不
No.
现在不行
Not right now.
半小时
A half-Hour.
那就补货啊 你有要货的电话吧
No, so go ahead and fill it up. You got the order number, right?
- 伙计 走快点 - 这太扯了
- Man, move your ass. - Man, this some bullshit.
我老妈会担心的 你们是在绑票
My mom's gonna be worried and shit. Y'all kidnapping niggas.
我是Colvin警长
I'm major colvin.
我叫Colvin警长
My name is major colvin.
- 啥警长 - 长你个头啊 混球
- Major what? - Major these, motherfucker.
我们下午把你们带到这来...
And we had to bring you down here this afternoon...
是因为你们不听我们警探的安排
Because you've not been complying with our directives.
说什么
Say what?
你们没按我们要求的做
You haven't been doing what we asked you to do.
嘿
Yo.
等我说完
When i'm done.
我要撒尿
I gotta pee now.
他不是说笑的 他闻起来像是尿裤子了
He ain't playing. Smell like he already pissed in his drawers.
好吧 去吧
All right, go ahead.
嘿 我也要去
Yo, i gotta go, too.
你得等会
Well, you're just gonna have to wait.
你让他去了 怎么能区别对待
You just let him go, how you gonna discriminate?
同性恋 你摸我屁股干嘛
Yo, faggy, why you touch my butt?
够了
That's enough!
玩笑结束了
The fun is over.
Tyrell 你今天怎么没来学校
Tyrell, why weren't you in school today?
我胃痛 离不开厕所
My stomach hurt. I couldn't make it out the bathroom.
跟我说话时要站起来 年轻人
Stand up when i talk to you, young man.
我认识你妈妈 Tyrell
I know your mother, tyrell.
她养的可不是个小丑 对吧
She didn't raise any clowns, now, did she?
对 女士
No, ma'am.
交给你了 警长
It's yours, major.
女士们先生们
Now, ladies and gentlemen,
我们把你们带到这来...
We brought you down here because...
是让你们知道...
You're here to learn about the new way...
我们对街角的新举措
The new way that we're going to do things on the corners.
- 那是市区 - 对
- That's downtown. - Yeah.
- 这就说得通了 - 共四个
- Well, that makes no sense. - All four.
来吧 严刑逼供吧 问我这两天去了哪
Go ahead, rip me a new asshole. Ask me where i've been for two days.
你说吧 牛人
Tell us, hotshot.
大学登记员交出了Stringer的课表
College registrar gives up stringer's course schedule.
我跟踪他到他住处 市区的大楼
I tail him to where he's laying his head. Downtown high-Rise.
租约上是本名 没有藏头藏尾
Name's on the lease, too. No attempt to hide it.
第二天我早起 跟踪他到一个午餐会...
I get up early next morning, follow him from his door to a lunch meeting...
跟州议员共餐
With the state senator.
就是上次被我们抓包那个
Same one with the bagman we bounced the last time around.
桌上还有几个白人 我都不认识
Couple of white guys at the table, too, nobody i read.
Stringer时不时会打手机...
And all the while, stringer's using his cell phone...
若无其事的在几个西装革履的家伙 面前打电话
Making calls in front of these suits like it ain't no thing.
靠 我甚至自己打了个
Shit, i even rang it up myself.
从招生表中弄来的号码
Got his number from an admissions form.
那号码不会是8447393吧
The number wouldn't be 844-7393?
我让Prez从巡回法庭要来了...
I had prez pull the b and b property assessments...
BB的财产评估和土地转让协议
And land transfers from circuit court.
某些文件要求电话号码
Some of the paperwork asked for a contact number.
因此这孩子如此自在地 使用电话也不奇怪了
So i'm not surprised our boy's using his cell phone so freely.
这些是他接听和拨打的电话
Those, right there, are the incoming and outgoing numbers on his phone.
几乎所有的都是市区交易所的
And damn near all of them are downtown exchanges.
建筑公司 城市许可证申请...
Architectural firms, city licensing...
律师行 城市规划办公室
Attorneys, zoning offices.
甚至还有商会的校园交易所
Even campus exchanges over at bccc.
你说他是清白的?
You saying he's right?
我说他的电话是清白的
I'm saying the phone is right.
账户信息表明他这个号码...
Account information confirms he's had that number listed...
用好一阵了
For quite a while.
干得好
Nice work.
也许因为他要保留那号码 所以那号码是清白的
Maybe the cell phone is clean because he's keeping it.
如果是干些勾当 可能会用即弃的
If it was dirty, it'd probably be a burner.
一次性的
Disposables.
Yo-Tech的新产品
The latest in yo-Tech.
他们用即弃手机打几个电话就扔掉
They make a couple of calls with a burner, throw it away.
再换一部 继续这样
Go on to the next phone, do the same.
在西Baltimore 这些东西在街上到处都是
There's more of those things laying around the streets of west baltimore...
比小瓶还多
Than empty vials.
这东西他妈的怎么监听
Well, how the fuck you supposed to get a wire up on that?
是啊 先是公用电话和呼机
Yeah, well, first it was payphone and pagers.
接着是手机和面谈 现在是这个
Then it was cell phones and face-To-Face meets. Now this.
这些混球真学得乖
The motherfuckers do learn.
每次我们要抓到他们 他们就学习并改变
Every time we come at them, they learn and adjust.
这么说...
So...
- 逮不到Stringer - 你们知道 几年前...
- Stringer's out of reach. - You know, a couple of years ago...
当他们买进市区的房地产...
When they were buying up all that downtown real estate...
我以为他们是买来等联邦的资金到位...
I thought they were buying it to flip it...
政府征用房产时...
And get the cash when the federal payout money lands...
转手套现
And the properties are condemned.
Bell和Barksdale从没卖过 他们还继续买 事实上...
Bell and barksdale haven't sold any of it. They're buying more, in fact...
还申请了建筑许可
And applying for building permits.
看样子Stringer Bell比毒贩更坏
Seems that stringer bell is worse than a drug dealer.
他是个开发商
He's a developer.
老天 他真的合法?
Jesus, fuck, he's really legit?
你也是个真的警察
Well, you real police.
既然他现在公开化了 你干嘛不拉他出来问问
Now that he's out in the open, why don't you pull him up and ask him?
你要几天时间 我可以拖住Daniels 但那之后...
You need a few days, i'll stall daniels. But after that...
你拿个我们能办的案子回来...
You come home with a case we can use...
否则就咽下你那该死的自尊回到组织里来
Or you swallow your goddamn pride and rejoin this unit.
你好吗 Donette?
How you doing, donette?
"我很好 String 我想你 宝贝"
"I'm fine, string. I missed you, baby."
听着 我很抱歉没回你电话
Look, i'm sorry for not returning them calls.
"抱歉"不会在夜里温暖我的床
"Sorry" don't keep my bed warm at night.
美女 我东奔西走
Shorty, i been running.
我不是想疏远你
Ain't like i'm trying to shut you out.
只是有生意要做 知道吗
I just got business to attend to, you know?
你知道孤单一人在这什么感受吗
Do you know how it feels to be alone out here?
警察找上门来 却没人在我身边
Police coming to my door, and i got no one to stand beside me.
你说警探给你留了张名片?
You say the detective left you a card?
他说D'angelo不是自杀
Man say d'angelo wasn't no suicide.
他脖子上的痕迹什么的
Something about the way the marks was on his neck.
他说D可能是被谋杀的
He said d could have been murdered and shit.
坐下
Sit down.
听我说
Now listen to me.
牢里的人都知道Avon是谁
Everyone in them walls know who avon is.
没人敢动他的侄子
Ain't nobody gonna do his nephew.
好吗
All right?
而我们的情况...
Now, as far as you and me go...
跟你保持距离是我的错...
I did you wrong by keeping you at arm's length...
但我不会再这样了
But it ain't gonna be like that no more.
噢耶
Oh, yeah.
上帝造化
God made that.
不会是意外
Couldn't be no accident.
你干嘛今晚请客 说实话
So why am i on your tab tonight? Tell the truth.
她最好别再从我旁边经过
I dare that to walk by me again. She better not.
你为什么请客 Bunk?
Why you buying, bunk?
死了俩...
I got two dead...
像是在Pimlico发生毒品纠纷
In what feels like a drug rip up in pimlico.
现场的年轻人貌似认出了Omar的人
And the young 'uns out on the scene, they seem to know this omar fella by sight.
我要Omar Jimmy
I need omar, jimmy.
又来? 老天 Bunk
Again? Jesus, bunk.
是啊
Yeah.
去他的
Fuck it, then.
3号方案?
Number three?
这法子你上次用过了 就音乐酒吧那个金发美女
No, that worked for you last time. The blonde at the juke.
噢 我真喜欢她
Oh, i really liked her.
接吻时人都会喜欢对方
Everybody likes everybody when they're kissing.
但不了 那边的朋友...
But no, my friend down there...
我想该用二号方案
She's a number two, i think.
待会要是问起来 就说我妈一周前过世了
And when it comes up, my mother passed. A week ago.
我不太能接受现实
And i'm having a little trouble getting over it.
所以我今晚很抑郁
That's why i'm feeling so blue tonight.
- 好吧 你妈过世了 你很悲伤 - 对
- Okay, your mom's dead and you're sad. - Yeah.
真是我死党
You my boy.
一样
The same way.
我妈一周前过世了...
My mom died about a week ago, and...
- 嘿 - 你好啊 老大?
- Yo. - What's up, boss?
你从Virginia Run拿到电话账单了吗
You got the phone receipts from the virginia run?
好
All right.
从今以后 你来处理这些
From now on, i want you to deal with these.
好的
All right.
如果Bernard 按照我们说的做 让他们运转起来...
If my man bernard doing it like we said and making them runs...
我就不想再管这些了
Then i don't wanna have to deal with this no more.
好的
For sure.
- 还有如果Donette打给我... - 我知道
- And if donette call me... - I know.
- 告诉那贱货你很忙 - 不
- Tell that bitch you busy. - No.
我要接电话
I'm gonna take the call.
Ronnie?
Ronnie Ronnie
Ronnie, ronnie!
Rhonda
Rhonda!
他严重涉嫌指使并导致了...
He was strongly suspected to have ordered or caused the deaths...
多人死亡 涉嫌
Of over a dozen individuals. Suspected.
这是谣言和含沙射影
It's rumor and innuendo.
这封信里没有一项指控不是...
There isn't one new allegation in this letter that wasn't already raised...
州助理检察官在庭审上提出的
By the assistant state's attorney at the time of the trial.
鉴于我当事人去年在这一监狱监禁期间...
And given my client's superlative record during his incarceration...
的良好记录 鉴于他指证服药过量死亡事件...
And given his notable role in identifying the source of the overdose deaths...
始作俑者的忠诚表现...
At this facility last year...
我恭敬地请求你们依照既定协议...
I respectfully ask that you honor our existing agreement...
准许Barksdale先生提早获释
And approve mr. Barksdale's early release.
胡说八道
That's bullshit!
少作评论 长官
Hold your comments, trooper.
我们承诺过 律师
We made a commitment, counselor.
鉴于一年前这一机构所面对的情况... 现在完全该兑现
And given what this institution was dealing with a year ago...
Rockefeller Rockefellers上市
Rockefeller! Rockefellers on the spot!
伙计 就是那边那个 G35里那个 伙计
Man, that's him right there. In that g35, man.
- 穿复古装那个? - 那衣服很抢手
- Boy in the retro? - That shit is tight.
430块 最好是这个价
$430, it better be.
该死 我也要搞一件
Hell, yeah. I'm gonna get me one of those motherfuckers.
那你得搞件Muggsy Bogues的(矮个NBA运动员)
You must be going to get that muggsy bogues, then.
你穿那件Unseld一定穿不着(华盛顿子弹队41号)
Your mini-Me ass gonna be swimming in that unseld.
跟平时一样 你们老搞错重点
As usual, man, y'all fools are missing my point.
那小子上周少给了钱...
That boy came up short on that money last week...
现在你们都看见他在这叫卖了 那钱哪去了
And y'all see how he out here grinding. So where that money at?
你们别光看他开的和穿的
You need to look beyond what he driving or wearing on his back.
那小子有女友吗
That boy got a girlfriend?
他跟个高中的小毒友在一起
He run with this little freak up at the high school.
她戴钻石吗
She wearing ice?
我就记得她戴个洋葱
She wearing a onion, that's about all i can remember.
该死 没错
Hell, yeah.
查查那女孩
Yo, check out the girl.
高中女生戴的铂金项链 只可能有一个来源
High school girl with platinum around her neck, only one place it came from.
给他家伙
Give my man his thing.
西格绍尔 不是Lorcin的 伙计
Sig sauer. That ain't no lorcin, dawg.
我用惯了左轮 伙计 点38不会卡壳
I'm used to revolvers, man.. 38 don't jam.
也别用15的
Don't hold 15, neither.
游戏还真变了
Game done changed.
游戏还是游戏 只是更狂暴了
Game the same. Just got more fierce.
我不是很想度假
I'm not big on vacations.
嗯 谁有时间啊
Yeah, who has time?
周末带孩子去滨海城市之类的怎样
What about taking the boys down to ocean city for a weekend or something?
你出过海吗
You ever been down the ocean?
听着
Listen.
并不是我等着Rhonda敞开怀抱
It wasn't like i was waiting for an opening with rhonda.
它就这么自然发生了
It just happened.
我该早点告诉你的
I should have told you sooner.
我得确信这不会让你我有龃龉
I need to know this isn't going to be a thing between you and me.
不 我祝福你们
No, i wish you both all the best.
我昨晚很吵吗
Was i very loud last night?
谢谢你没让我尴尬
Thanks for making this easy on me.
你走吗
You coming?
不 我想多待会 理一理思绪
No, i think i'll stay here a while, nurse this.
然后再走
Then i'll shove off.
再来一杯 在旁边放杯啤酒
One more, and put a beer next to it.
伙计 最近可好
Nigga, what's up?
你好吗
You good?
你看起来不错
Yo, lookin' good.
看看你  不错哦
Look at you, all right.
开始了
Shit is on.
要的就是这个
This what i'm talking about.
喝了吧
Drink that shit.
我很惊讶Avon让你们出来狂欢
I'm surprised avon be letting y'all get your heads up.
有时就得这样
Sometimes you got to.
亲吻天空吧 伙计
Kiss the sky, nigga.
- 可以走了吗 - 嗯 你还能开车吗
- Ready to go? - Yeah. Are you all right to drive?
我还以为你是今晚的指定司机呢
I thought you were the designated driver tonight.
我没事 真的 我可以开
No, i'm good, really. I'm good to go.
晚安
Good night.
一个一条腿名叫Aaliyah的贱货
Bitch with one leg named aaliyah.
那算什么啊
What kind of shit is that?
靠
Oh, shit.
你还是喜欢女人的吧
You do still like females, don't you?
靠
Shit.
他回家咯
He home now.